DJABER BOUKETIR

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of birth: December 21, 2004 Place of birth: Ain Oulmane

Direct 5 11001100. 100040, 07020110007

Gender: Male

Nationality: Algerian Civil status: Single

PROFILE

I am Djaber Boukthir, third-year computer science student at the University of Ferhat Abbas Setif, Algeria, I'm a highly motivated and dedicated individual with a passion for excellence and helping others. Thanks to these qualities, I have developed a diverse skill set encompassing public speaking, design, development, training, organization, and leadership.

I served as the **president of the Setif Scientific Club** for a year and facilitated numerous workshops and courses in UI/UX and front-end development for university students, both on and off-campus, for two consecutive years.

As a **certified Train-the-Trainer in STEAM from World Learning Algeria**, I have conducted various workshops and courses in LEGO robotics, UI/UX, and front-end development for children under 18, in collaboration with World Learning and Bright School.

I have also taught Arduino at King's Academy to children under 11.

I worked as a **freelancer** for a period and am currently employed as a UI/UX designer and front-end developer at a **startup**.

EDUCATION

L3 Computer science student

2024

UFAS1, setif

Bac Electrical engineering in High school

2022

laarbi blilita, Ain Oulmane, setif

Steam Teacher Training

Nov 2023 - May 2024

World learning Algeria, Setif

Best practices in steam teaching lesson planning, universal design for learning, project-Based learning, Design thinking, Reflective Practice & Peer teacher training and Robotics education. https://algeria.worldlearning.org/algiers-steam-center/

EMPLOYMENT

Steam teacher (Arduino and web dev)

May 2024 - Present Kings Academy, Ain Oulmane, Setif

Arduino for kids (8-11) years

https://www.facebook.com/KingsAcademyedu

The president of the Setif Scientific Club

Sep 2023 - Present

UFAS1, Setif

I served as the president of the Setif Scientific Club for a year and facilitated numerous workshops and courses in UI/UX and front-end development for university students, both on and off-campus, for two consecutive years.

An effective organizational method was used to revive the club from hibernation. https://www.instagram.com/setifian.scientific.club/

SKILLS		
front end	Back end	
uı/ux	Design	
Public speaking	Steam teaching	
Management		
HOBBIES		
■ Anime watching	■ video games	
■ philosophy	■ Volunteer work	